

# **Altes Idriz**

### Junior JavaScript Developer

A web developer specializing in JavaScript and React. With two years as a technical manager and six years as a sales manager, I bring a unique blend of technical expertise and business acumen. Currently enhancing my skills through ongoing web development studies, I am eager to contribute my proficiency and dedication to innovative projects.

■ altes.fidail@gmail.com

**Q** 0899 95 98 36

Sofia Bulgaria

in linkedin.com/in/altes.idriz

Ohttps://github.com/altesidriz



### **EDUCATION**

### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

#### Software University

09/2021 - Present Professional Modules

#### JavaScript Advanced

A course for in-depth knowledge of the JavaScript language. Working with the DOM tree, manipulations on it, and handling events. Functional and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) approaches in JavaScript, inheritance, object composition, prototype chains and etc.

#### JavaScript Applications

HTTP requests, REST services, Backend as a Service (BaaS), asynchronous code (Promises, use of async/await), templating, and routing. Creating a Single Page Application.

#### HTML and CSS

"Knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3 for web development, web browsers, tools for HTML/CSS/DOM development, and practical skills in using the language for describing web content (HTML) and the language for styling web content (CSS).

#### JavaScript Back-End

"The development of server-side JavaScript applications on the Node.js platform, using Express.js as a framework. Server-client architecture and data-driven web applications with Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB. Working with MongoDB-Mongoose library. Building REST APIs using Express.js and MongoDB."

#### ReactJS

"Developing Single Page Applications using ReactJS technology. Writing with JSX syntax, handling requests and Promises,routing, form validation,styling components using techniques like CSS Modules and Styled Components. React Hooks, Context API.Unit testing with JEST."

#### Software Technologies and Design

**PU Plovdiv** 

09/2019 - Present

### **Transport Engineering**

**UACEG Sofia** 

09/2008 - 07/2015



# WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Technical Manager/Road Constructions**

**Global Transport Engineering** 

03/2015 - 01/2016

### **Technical Manager in Civil Constructions**

**ELER Kaldera** 

04/2019 - 02/2020

## Sales Manager

**REM Engineering 08** 

02/2016 - Present



### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

### **Programming Languages**

Js Java Script

F HTML5

₹ css3

👙 Java

©C#

**Frameworks** 

React

⊖X ExpressJS

NodeJS
■
NodeJS
Node

**Databases** 

MongoDB▶ Firebase

Tools

✓ Visual Studio Code

Web Storm

**⋈** Visual Studio

Inteli, LIDE



#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Attention to detail

**Communication Analysis** 

Teamwork & cooperation Analysis



# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### Booking Page @

Full stack web application, written in JavaScript with React, Express, MongoDB, JWT and MVC pattern (in progress)

#### Car Offer Page @

Full stack web application, written in JavaScript with React, Express, MongoDB and MVC pattern (in progress)



#### **LANGUAGES**

### Bulgarian

Native

**English** 

Turkish

Native